kaki narase sonzai wo
rock away your existence
koko ni iru to
shouting that you are here
arata na tabi ga ima hajimaru
a new journey begins now
kawari yuku kisetsu no naka wo ikinuku tabi ni bokura
as we survived through the changing seasons
chie to tsuyosa wo te ni ireta kedo JUST LOOKS LIKE SURVIVAL GAME
we gained knowledge and strength (just looks like a survival game)
nagareteku jikan no naka ni
but the forgotten memories
okizari ni shita omoi wo
of the feelings abandoned within the flows of time
wasureta koto sura wasurete ita
have also been lost
kuzure kaketa toki kodoku wo shitte
when sinking down we learned loneliness
deaeta bokura hitori ja nai
but now we've met each other we are no longer alone
sarake dase kanjou wo banjou no omoi wo
unveil your feelings those high emotions
namidame ga unmei wo kaete yuku
those tears will change your fate
yami ni uchi narase kodou wo
pound your heartbeat against the darkness
kitto aeru yo onaji itami no hata no moto de
we're sure to meet under the same flag of pain
Sorry, sorry.
Was that some eagle poop
just now?
Nothing there, huh?
Well, I worked up a sweat,
so I guess I'll go home
and take a shower.
Legend of Leaf Village
Onba Existed!!
I worked up
a good sweat today too.
What's the deal, Akamaru?
He says you smell bad, Naruto.
Are you making sure
to take a bath?
Don't be saying rude things!
No, you seriously stink.
Come to think of it...
The poop from the eagle
a moment ago might...
Sakura.
Oh, I found a slacker
who can't get a mission!
That's just...
I'm not that much a slacker!
So it seems. You must've done
some reckless training.
It's ripped.
You're right. I didn't notice!
It can't be helped.
Bring it to me later.
I'll sew it up for you.
Really?! Really?! Really?!
Sakura, you're such a nice person.
It's the first time in my life...
you've been this nice to me!
Hey, Naruto. You're exaggerating.
Naruto!
What're you doing, Sakura?!
You touched my breast
just now, didn't you?!
I didn't do anything like that!
Then, what're those hairy hands
sticking out from your armpit?!
What's... that?
What's this?!
Your back.
What in the world is this?!
It's a huge poop!
Idiot! That's some kind of creature!
— Is it a caterpillar?!
— What?! Get it off.
No, this is an animal.
Let go!
Give me a break.
You guys, have you ever heard
of the legend of Onbaa?
Onbaa?
I've never heard of it!
Shizune! You don't know?
Nope. Is that legend something like
an old tale or something?
That's what I thought, but...
Long ago when I was young,
I heard about a legend...
A legend about a dangerous,
hairy, bear-like creature called Onbaa
who lived deep in the mountains
near the village...
One day, that idiot Jiraiya
eagerly went into the forest
saying he was going to investigate
the Onbaa
for his summer vacation
independent research.
The Pervy Sage?
Yes...
Are you an idiot?
Do you seriously think
there's an Onbaa?
Well, you'll get yours when
you see my independent research!
Who would?
Even if there were an Onbaa,
it wouldn't deal with you...
You said it! Flat-chested girl!
Who's flat-chested?!
No way is there such a thing
as an Onbaa!
You wanna bet on that?
Yeah! I'll bet!
Then, I'll bet on Jiraiya.
Then, I'm off to wrestle
with an Onbaa!
And? Did the Pervy Sage
meet an Onbaa?
When he came back three days later,
he said he won with
a force-out move...
which most likely was a lie.
Here it is.
What's this?
What lousy writing!
You're one to talk, Naruto.
Let's see... The Onbaa is big.
It is nine-feet tall.
The Onbaa is scary.
No one is a match for it
when it gets mad.
But I beat it at wrestling.
What's this?
The Onbaa's child likes
being carried piggyback.
They grow up on the parent's back.
What?!
What Jiraiya wrote is bogus,
tracing the legend as is, but...
So there was an Onbaa...
Grandma Tsunade, as for this thing,
it stays piggyback on my back
and won't get off.
What should I do?
According to legend,
the child Onbaa considers
the first thing it sees after birth
as its parent
and clings to the back
of that person.
It seems they grow that way,
piggybacked on the parent,
until they become an adult.
It seems until then,
they never leave the parent's back.
Then, there's no other way
but to wait until it grows up.
You say that, but when it grows up...
it'll turn into a scary
nine-foot tall monster, right?
What's up with
that straightforward reaction?
Well, it's a legend,
so it'll probably get off eventually...
Don't be so irresponsible!
Hang in there, Naruto...
We'll be cheering you on
from behind the scenes.
Come up close rather than
behind the scene, damn it!
What is it?
I won't lose, you know!
This isn't a weight, man!
What is it, Hinata?
Naruto... I heard a strange rumor.
A strange rumor... you say?
That you... had a child.
You mean this?
Hinata!
Hey! You okay?! Hinata!
Hinata, Hinata!
Hinata?!
What's the deal?
You're sure an extravagant guy...
Am I going to have to take a bath
every time he pees on me?
"ICHIRAKU RAMEN"
You know, we don't allow pets.
The Leaf Village public health
department is strict, you see.
I missed dinner because of him.
Overlook it just for today.
But now that I look closer,
he's cute, isn't he?
So, what's his name?
He's saying it himself,
so I guess Onbu is okay.
Onbu, huh...?
Doesn't he want to eat
some Naruto fish cake?
Here.
Old man!
Give me a whole roll of Naruto!
Coming right up!
Ever since you clung to my back,
I've been getting nothing
but odd jobs like this.
Well, I guess it can't be helped...
He's gotten big...! And so quickly...
This is bad!
Uzumaki Naruto,
you are assigned a mission
for the removal of the mountain bandits
from Yamabuki Pass!
Removal? Hey, old lady...
Onbu's gotten big,
so you intend to get rid
of the troublemaker, right?
No, it's not like that.
I was thinking you've had
some eye-opening growth recently, so...
Then, what about the other members?
No...
Since you've shown
such remarkable growth,
a solo infiltration should be fine.
Sure enough,
it's getting rid of the troublemaker!
This is also fate...
Okay, now, back to work.
Thanks, mister!
Naruto, Naruto.
Things are fun when
you're around, Onbu!
That Grandma Tsunade.
Don't think you were able to
get rid of the troublemaker so easily.
I'll beat the mountain bandits
and finish up this mission lickety-split
and the two of us will return
to the Leaf Village with pride!
Right, Onbu?!
Hey! Mountain bandits! Come out!
Who're you, creep?!
Who're you?!
What do you want?!
I'm Uzumaki Naruto with my kid Onbu!
Prepare yourselves!
— Say what?!
— Get him!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Onbu!
Even knowing it's a clone...
I won't forgive those who hurt Onbu!
How was that?!
Die!
Onbu! You saved me!
Onbu... I owe you my life.
Let's get back to the village quick
and surprise everyone!
Onbu! No way will I believe
that you're a dangerous creature!
We'll go as the Onbu-Naruto team
succeeding the Kiba-Akamaru team!
What was that?
It's okay...
You've got me with you.
Onbu?! No, it's huge!
Could it be... you're after Onbu?
Are you Onbu's mom?!
Wait! I didn't steal him!
Onbu! Say something, will you?!
You idiot, Onbu!
No, you've got the wrong idea!
Onbu, it's your mom.
It's not my intention!
Damn it! I had a rough time of it.
If you're a mother,
then take better care
of your child, really!
It's okay! I'll return Onbu to you!
So rest easy.
My body got light.
Onbu? You got so big!
Wha...? What's the matter, Onbu?!
What's the deal?!
Wait... Onbu, it's me!
Can't you tell?!
We were getting along
so well just a moment ago!
Please remember me!
It's me! Naruto U-zu-ma-ki!
Oh, yeah! Naruto!
Naruto! Naruto!
Onbu, look at this!
Remember! Remember this spiral!
Naruto, Naruto!
You remember my back
you clung to the whole time, don't you?
Have I... had it?
Onbu...
I'm tired...
This feels kind of good...
It's like I'm being carried piggyback.
Onbu...
Onbu!
Live in good health with your mom.
All right!
My sides... are splitting!
Onbaa is now no longer a legend.
They're thriving in the village forest
and seriously proliferating.
The stupid eagles carried them in, so...
Naruto! How'd you tear it off you?!
Tell me!
Who knows?
All I did was wrestle with Onbu.
Don't be so mean!
At this rate,
the village will be crushed.
Tell me! Naruto!
Don't look at me.
kinou wa Call Sign zenbu keitai de
yesterday's call sign was broadcast all from my phone
norenai Fuzz Guitar henna kouen de
in a strange park I play the fuzz guitar without enthusiasm
Yellow Moon
yellow moon
ima mo mittsu kazoete me wo akete
even now, counting to three I open my eyes
Shadow Moon mada yume wo miteru
shadow moon, I am still dreaming
me wo mite me wo mite se wo mukeai nagara
look at my eyes, look at my eyes, as we face one another's back
me wo mite itsu aeru
look at my eyes, when can we meet?
Every Day Every Night omoi tsuku kotoba de
every day, every night, with every word I can think of
chirakatta mama no kimochi wo ima sugu
right away, my messy feelings as is
mahou no Chord Change nemurenai machi
a magical chord change in a restless city
higawari na Jazz Guitar sotto mainaa de
a daily jazz guitar played in a soft minor key
Shino and I have been
sent to a certain village to deal with
a dispute over a family head
who passed away.
An old woman suddenly appears
on the road and says this to us.
"Even dead men laugh
in Motoyoshi Village"
They were mysterious words.
I never imagined it at this time.
To think I would see with
my own eyes,
a sight in this village too frightening
to even talk about...
Next: "Shino Laughs."
I can't even go to the bathroom
alone at night.